[
    {
        "numb": 1,
        "question": "Artificial Intelligence is about?",
        "answer": "Making a machine Intelligent",
        "options": [
            "Making a machine Intelligent",
            "Playing a game on Computer",
            "Programming on Machine with your Own Intelligence",
            "Putting your intelligence in Machine"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 2,
        "question": "Who is known as the -Father of AI?",
        "answer": "John McCarthy",
        "options": [
            "Allen Newell",
            "Alan Turing",
            "Fisher Ada",
            "John McCarthy"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 3,
        "question": "A field of study that investigates the impact of individuals, groups, and structure on behaviour within organization is known as:",
        "answer": "organizational behaviour",
        "options": [
            "psychology",
            "organizational behaviour",
            "social psychology",
            "anthropology"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 4,
        "question": "Select the most appropriate situation for that a blind search can be used",
        "answer": "Small Search Space",
        "options": [
            "Real-life situation",
            "Complex game",
            "Small Search Space",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 5,
        "question": "Which of the following topics is generally considered to be outside the field of OB?",
        "answer": "therapy",
        "options": [
            "therapy",
            "employment turnover",
            "job satisfaction",
            "absenteeism"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 6,
        "question": "Among the given options, which search algorithm requires less memory?",
        "answer": "Depth First Search",
        "options": [
            "Linear Search",
            "Depth First Search",
            "Breadth-First Search",
            "Optimal Search"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 7,
        "question": "are defined as people who oversee the activities of others and who are responsible for attaining goals in organizations",
        "answer": "Managers",
        "options": [
            "Apprentices",
            "Interns",
            "Secretaries",
            "Managers"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 8,
        "question": "If a robot is able to change its own trajectory as per the external conditions, then the robot is considered as the",
        "answer": "Intelligent",
        "options": [
            "Intelligent",
            "Mobile",
			"Non-Servo",
			"Open Loop"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 9,
        "question": "As the instructions can deal with variable size operands we use ____________ to resolve this.",
        "answer": "Size indicator mnemonic",
        "options": [
            "None of the mentioned",
            "Size indicator mnemonic",
            "Special assemblers",
            "Delimiter"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 10,
        "question": "Which of the given language is not commonly used for AI?",
        "answer": "Perl",
        "options": [
            "LISP",
            "PROLOG",
            "Perl",
            "Python"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 11,
        "question": "A technique that was developed to determine whether a machine could or could not demonstrate the artificial intelligence known as the",
        "answer": "Turing Test",
        "options": [
            "Boolean Algebra",
            "Turing Test",
            "Logarithm",
            "Algorithm"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 12,
        "question": "The component of an Expert system is",
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "options": [
            "Knowledge Base",
            "Inference Engine",
            "User Interface",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 13,
        "question": "An AI agent perceives and acts upon the environment using_?",
        "answer": "Both a and c",
        "options": [
            "Sensors",
            "Perceiver",
            "Actuators",
            "Both a and c"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 14,
        "question": "Which rule is applied for the Simple reflex agent?",
        "answer": "Condition-action rule",
        "options": [
            "Condition-action rule",
            "Simple &Condition-action rule",
            "Control Unit",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 15,
        "question": "The PC register holds what?",
        "answer": "The address for the next instruction",
        "options": [
            "The accumulated memory location",
            "The instruction for the next instruction",
            "The data for the next instruction",
            "The address for the next instruction"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 16,
        "question": "Which of these is not a system utility program?",
        "answer": "A graphics card driver",
        "options": [
            "Memory and CPU monitor",
            "A graphics card driver",
            "Defragmentation software",
            "Diagnostic software in case of computer crash"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 17,
        "question": "Which agent deals with the happy and unhappy state?",
        "answer": "Utility-based agent",
        "options": [
            "Compression",
            "Model-based agent",
            "Goal-based Agent",
            "Defragmentation"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 18,
        "question": "Rational agent always does the right things",
        "answer": "True",
        "options": [
            "false",
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 19,
        "question": "Which AI technique enables the computers to understand the associations and relationships between objects and events?",
        "answer": "Pattern Matching",
        "options": [
            "Relative Symbolism",
            "Pattern Matching",
            "Cognitive Science",
            "Heuristic Processing"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 20,
        "question": "The exploration problem is where_?",
        "answer": "Agent contains the knowledge of State and actions.",
        "options": [
            "Agent contains the knowledge of State and actions.",
            "Agent does not contain the knowledge of State and actions.",
            "Only actions are known to the agent.",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    }
]
    